Do you have your driver's license?
Yeah...
I think so...
Well, well
If it isn't Jon from Arnarfjord
Don't you remember me
Sven?
Sven from Sugandafjord
Umm...
We sometimes met up
between fishing tours back in the day
You were dating...
Some girl from Patreksfjord
What was her name again?
Berg-something
Bergrun or Bergljot
Jon from Arnarfjord
That's your mother, right?
Yep
Hello there, ma'am
You remember
me...?
Hmm...
And what...
Where are you headed?
South
To Reykjavik?
Eyrarbakki
Mmm...
Eyrarbakki? Got relatives there?
My mom
Your mom has relatives there?
Yes
Huh
Plan on staying long?
Mom is going to rest there
What...
Do they have a sanatorium there?
Huh?
Yes, like a temporary rest-stay place
She doesn't need rest, she's dead.
Uh... Jon
Your driver's license
is getting a little worn
And I have to encourage you to have the car
inspected at your earliest convenience
Or just go to the next car repair shop
I really should ground your car right here and now
But you know, for old times sake
And not to mention your mother
I'm going to give you an opportunity
To rectify this
I don't say this very often, but
Try to drive a little faster
Or take the local gravel roads,
that may be best for you
Okay?
Hey, are you...
Going to watch the comet tonight?
It's going to be spectacular....
Safe travels, Jon