Do you have a driver's license?
Yeah, I think so
Hah
Jon from Arnarfjord
Don't you remember me?
Sven?
Sven from Sugandafjord
We sometime met up between
fishing tours back in the day
You were dating some girl from Patro
What was her name again?
Berg-something, Bergrun or Bergljot
Hah
Jon from Arnarfjord
Ah
Is rhat your mother?
Yep
Hello there, ma'am
You might remember me?
Oh
Where are you headed?
South
To Reykjavik?
Eyrarbakki
Aah, do you have any relatives in Eyrarbakki?
My mom
Your mom has relatives there?
Yes
Hmm
Plan on staying long?
She is going to rest there
What
Do they have a sanatorium in Eyrarbakki?
What?
Like a temporary rest-stay place
She doesn't need to rest, she's dead
Listen... Jon
Your driver's license is getting a little worn
And I have to encourage you to have
the car inspected as soon as possible
You should really just go to the next car repair shop
I really should ground your car right here and now
But because of old times sakes
And not to mention your mother, I'm going to
Give you an opportunity to...
Rectify this
I don't say this very often, but
Try to drive a little faster
Or take the less frequently used roads
I think that might be best for you
Okay?
Oh, yeah,
Are you going to watch the comet tonight?
It's going to be spectacular
Safe travels