Damn it.
Hey.
Come out.
What are you thinking, huh?
Where the hell did you learn to drive, man?
Listen, no need to get violent.
Violent?
How is one supposed to react to attempted murder, huh?
Attempted murder?
What are you thinking, huh?
You're endagering everybody here.
What are you doing?
You complete fucking idiot.
Good morning.
What is going on here?
Why don't you ask this neanderthal?
He's been putting us all in danger by
driving at 30km an hour on the highway.
Calm down please.
I am calm.
Come with me.
Am I being arrested?
For trying to promote some minimal traffic conduct, huh?
Take it easy, buddy. No one is being arrested.
Come and talk to me.
Shit.
Shit!
Well now...
how are we doing?
I'm doing fine.
That was quite the row of cars behind you.
Yep.
What are we talking about here?
The row of cars behind me...
At what speed were you driving?
The speedometer showed forty two.
That wouldn't exactly be called speeding.
Nope.
Listen...
That's unfortunately much too slow for the highway.
You're creating danger by driving so slow.
Do you have a driver's license?
Yes, I think so...
Well well,
Jon from Arnarfjord...
If it isn't Jon from Arnarfjord.
Don't you remember me?
Sven?
Sven from Sugandafjord like I was sometimes called?
We sometimes met up...
between fishing tours back in the day.
I'm sure it's been thirty or forty years.
You...
You were dating...
some girl from Patro.
What was her name again?
Berg-something...
Berg... Berg... run or... Bergljot.
Jon from Arnarfjord?
Is that your mother?
Yep.
Hello there, ma'am.
You remember me...?
And...
Where are you headed?
South.
Into town?
Eyrarbakki.
Eyrarbakki?
Got relatives there?
My mom.
Your mom got relative there?
Mhmm.
Okay...
Plan on staying long?
Mom is going to rest there.
Do they have a sanatorium there?
Huh?
Yes, like a temporary rest-stay place.
She doesn't need rest. She's dead.
Uh, Jon...
Your driver's license is getting a little worn.
And I have to encourage you to have the car inspected at your earliest convenience.
Or maybe go straight to a repair shop.
I really should ground your car right here and now.
But... you know, for old times sake...
and especially because of your mother.
I'm going to give you an opportunity to rectify this.
Alright?
Yes.
Yeah and, well I...
don't say this very often, but...
for God's sake, drive a little faster.
Or use less frequently used roads...
I think that would be best for you.
Okay...
Oh, are you going to watch...
the comet tonight.
It's going to be spectacular...
Okay then... Safe travels...
Maniac.