Fucking hell!
Get out!
Fuck!
Where the hell did you learn to drive, man?
What?
What's going on!
Violent?!
Huh?
How is one supposed to
react to attempted murder? Huh?
Attempted murder?
Yes!
What were you going to do?
Kill us all?
Huh?
Are you f...
Absolutely retarded?!
Huh?
What were you thinking?
What?
What is going on here?
Why don't you ask this neanderthal? Huh?
He's putting us all in danger by
driving at 30km an hour!
Hold your horses
Relax
Relax?
Why don't you come with
me over here for a second?
Am i being arrested for trying to
promote some minimal traffic conduct?
Take it easy, buddy. No one is being arrested
Come here and talk to me for a second
You are a complete idiot!
Well now, how are we doing?
I'm doing fine
What uh...
That was quite the row of cars behind you
Yep
What are we talking about here?
The row of cars behind me...
At what speed were you going?
The speedometer showed forty two
That wouldn't exactly be...
Called speeding
Nope
Listen, that's unfortunately much too slow
You're creating danger in the traffic
Do you have a driver's license?
Yeah, I think so...
Uh, hah
Jo- Jon, Jon from Arnarfjord is it really you?
Don't you remember me?
Sven?
Sven from Sugandafjord
We sometimes met up between fishing tours back in the day
I'm sure it's been thirty to forty years since
You were dating some girl from Patro
What was her name again? Berg-something. Bergljot or Bergrun
That's your mother, right?
Yep
Hello there, ma'am. You remember me...?
Where are you headed?
South
To Reykjavik?
Eyrarbakki
What?
Got relatives in Eyrarbakki?
My mom
Your mom has relatives there?
Yes
Yeah?
And how long do you plan to stay?
Uh
Mom is going to rest there
Do they have a sanatorium there?
What?
Yes, like a temporary rest-stay place?
She doesn't need to rest, she's dead
Uh... Jon
Your driver's license is getting a little worn
And I have to encourage you to have
the car inspected as soon as possible
Or even just go to the next car repair shop
I really should ground your car right here and now
But you know, for old times sake
I'm going to give you an opportunity to rectify this, okay?
Especially because of your mother
Well...
I don't say this often, but...
Try to drive a little faster
Or maybe
Use less frequently used roads,
that may be best for you
Okay?
Yep
Hey, are you...
Are you going to watch the comet tonight?
It'll be spectacular
Safe travels
Yes
Maniac!