Do you have your driver's license?
Yeah, I think so...
Well well
Jon from Arnarfjord?
Don't you remember me?
Sven?
Sven from Sugandafjord
We sometimes met up
between fishing tours back in the day.
Umm...
You were dating a girl from patro
What was her name again?
Berg-something, Bergrun or Bergljot
Jon from Arnarfjord
That's your mother, right?
Yep
Hello there, ma'am. You remember
me...?
Hmm?
Where are you headed?
South
To Reykjavik?
Eyrarbakki
Eyrarbakki?
Got relatives there?
My mom
Your mom has relatives there?
Yes
I see
Plan on staying long?
Mom is going to rest there
Do they have a sanatorium there?
Huh?
Yes, like a temporary rest-stay place
She doesn't rest, she's dead
Uh.. Jon
New Caption
And I have to encourage you to have
the car inspected at your earliest convenience.
Or just go to the next car repair shop
I really should...
Ground your car right here and now
Yes
But you know, for old times sake,
Especially because of your mother
I'm going to give you an opportunity to rectify this
Okay?
Well
I don't say this very often
Try to drive a little faster
Or take the less frequently used roads
That might be best for you?
Hey
Aren't you...
Going to watch the comet tonight?
It's going to be spectacular
Okay then....
Bye Jon. Safe travels