Hey.
Come out.
Come out!
Where the hell did you learn to drive, man?
Listen, no need to get violent.
Violent?
Huh?
Yes.
How is one supposed to react to attempted murder, huh?
Attempted murder?
Yes.
What are you thinking, man?
You endangered everyone here.
Only thinking about your own ass, huh?
Complete fucking ass...
Hello.
Alright...
What is going on here?
Why don't you ask this neanderthal?
He's been putting us all in danger by...
Driving around at 30km an hour on the highway.
Hold your horses.
Come talk to me for a second.
What are you doing?
Am I being arrested...
for trying to promote some minimal traffic conduct?
No one is being arrested.
Just come and talk to me for a second.
Fucking...
Shit.
Well now...
how are we doing?
I'm doing fine.
That was quite the row of cars behind you.
Yep.
What are we talking about here?
The row of cars behind me...
At what speed were you driving?
The speedometer showed forty two.
Mmm...
That wouldn't exactly be called speeding.
Nope.
No...
Listen...
That's unfortunately much too slow...
for the highway.
You're creating a lot of danger.
Do you have a driver's license?
Yes. I think so...
Ha!
Well well...
If it isn't Jon from Arnarfjord.
Don't you remember me?
Sven?
Sven from Sugangafjord like I was sometimes called?
We sometimes met up between fishing tours back in the day.
I'm sure it's been thirty or forty years.
You were dating a girl from Patro.
What was her name again?
Berg-something...
Bergljot or... Bergrun...
New Caption
Is that your mother?
Yep.
Hello there, ma'am.
You remember me...?
Mmm...
Where are you headed?
South.
Into town?
Eyrarbrakki.
Eyrarbakki?
Got relatives there?
My mom.
Your mom has relatives there?
Yes.
Okay...
Plan on staying long?
Mom is going to rest there.
Okay...
Do they have a sanatorium there?
Huh?
Yes, like a temporary rest-stay place.
She doesn't need to rest. She...
She doesn't need to rest. She's dead.
Uh, Jon...
Your driver's license is getting a little worn.
And I have to encourage you to have the car inspected...
at your earliest convenience.
Or maybe even just go to a repair shop.
I really should ground your car right here and now,
but... you know, for old times sake
and especially because of your mother...
I'm going to give you an opportunity to rectify this.
Alright?
And I...
don't say this ver often, but...
for Gods sake drive a little faster.
Or...
or just take...
less frequently used roads.
I think that would be best for you...
Are you going to...
watch the com...
the comet tonight.
It's going to be spectacular...
Okay then... Safe travels...