Fucking hell...
Hey!
Come out.
Fucking hell...
Hey!
Where the hell did you learn to drive, man? Huh...?
What's wrong with you, huh?
Listen, no need to get violent.
Violent?
Huh...?
How is one supposed to react to attempted murder, huh?
Attempted murder?
Idio...
What are you doing, huh?
You're endagering everyone.
Are you... are you... completely...
a complete idiot.
What are you thinking, huh?
Good morning.
Is everybody calm?
What is going on here?
Why don't you ask this maniac?
He's benn putting us all in danger.
Drives around at 30km an hour like some idiot.
Alright, calm down.
I am calm.
Okay, come talk to me for a second.
Hey, am I being arrested for trying to...
promote some minimal traffic conduct?
Buddy, no one is being arrested.
Just come and talk to me...
Stop it.
Well now...
how are we doing?
I'm doing fine.
That was quite the row of cars behind you.
Yep.
What are we talking about here?
The row of cars behind me...
At what speed were you driving?
The speedometer showed forty two.
That wouldn't exactly be called speeding.
Nope.
No...
Listen, that's way too slow...
You can't drive so slowon a highway, it creates so much danger.
Do you hav a driver's license?
Uhm...
Yes, I think so...
Well, well...
Jon...
If it isn't Jon from Arnarfjord.
Don't you remember me?
Sven.
Sven from Sugandafjord like I was sometimes called?
We sometimes met up between fishing tours back in the day.
I'm sure it's been thirty or forty years.
You were dating...
a girl from...
Patro.
What was her name again?
Berg-something... Bergljot or Bergrun...
Is that your mother?
Yep.
Hello there, ma'am.
You remember me...?
Where are you headed?
South.
Into town?
No, Eyrarbakki.
Ey... Eyrarbakki?
Got relatives there?
My mom.
Your mom has relatives there?
Yes.
Mmm...
Plan on staying long?
Mom is going to rest there.
Do they have a sanatorium there?
Huh?
Yes, like a temporary rest-stay place.
She doesn't need to rest. She's dead.
Uh, Jon...
You're driver's license is getting a little worn.
And I have to encourage you to have the car inspected at your earliest convenience.
Or just straight to a repair shop.
I really should ground your car right here and now...
but... you know, for old times sake,
and especially because of your mother...
I'm going to give you an opportunity to rectify this, alright?
Hey.
I don't say this very often...
but for god's sake, drive a little faster.
Or try to take less frequently used roads.
That would probably be best for you.
Oh, are you going to watch...
the comet tonight...
It's going to be spectacular...
Safe travels...