Do you have a driver's license?
I think so...
Well
Jon from Arnarfjord
Huh?
Don't you remember me?
Sven?
Sven from Sugandafjord like I was sometimes called
We sometimes met up between
fishing tours back in the day
Umm...
You were dating a girl from Flateyri
Wait, no, she was from Patro
Jon from Arnarfjord
Don’t you remember me?
Sven?
Sven from Sugundafjord
We sometimes met up between fishing tours back in the day
You were dating some girl from Patro
What was her name again?
Berg-something
Bergrun or Bergljot
Hah
Jon from Arnarfjord
Well
Isn't that your mother?
Yep
Hello there ma'am
You remember me...?
And...
Where are you headed?
South
To Reykjavik?
Eyrarbakki
Eyrarbakki?
Got any relatives there?
My mom
Your mom has relatives there
Yes
How long are you staying?
She is going to rest there
Is that so?
Do they have a sanatorium in Eyrarbakki?
What?
Like a temporary rest-stay place, right?
She doesn't need a rest-stay, she's dead
Yes
Look, Jon...
So...
Your driver's license is getting a little worn
And I have to encourage you to to have
the car inspected at your earliest convenience
Preferably at a car repair shop
I really should ground your car
right here and now, but...
But for old times sake
And not to mention your mother
I'm going to give you
an opportunity to rectify this
Okay?
Yeah and umm...
I don't say this very often, but
Drive a little faster
Or just use less frequently used roads
That may be best for you
Huh?
Oh
Are you...
Are you going to watch the comet tonight?
It's going to be spectacular
Okay, Jon
Safe travels, my friend