Shit!
Hey!
Come here!
Come out here!
Fucking hell!
Where the hell did you learn to
drive, man?
Hey, buddy
Where the hell did you learn to
drive, man?
Listen, no need to get violent
Violent?!
Huh?
How is one supposed to react
to attempted murder, huh?
Attempted murder?
What are you thinking? Are you intentionally trying to cause
a mass accident? Huh?
Shit!
Good day
What's going on here?
Why don't you ask this neanderthal?
He's been putting us all in danger by
driving at 30km an hour on the
highway.
Why don't you come
with me over here for a second?
Stop it!
Hey!
Come with me!
Am I being arrested for trying to
promote some minimal traffic conduct?
Take is easy, buddy. No one is being
arrested
Watch out!
Jesus!
Well now
How are we doing?
I'm doing fine
That was quite the row of cars behind
you
Yep
What are we talking about here?
"The row of cars behind me...."
At what speed were you driving?
The speedometer showed forty two
That wouldn't exactly be called
speeding
Nope
Hmm...
Listen, that's unfortunately much too
slow for the highway
You're
creating danger by driving so
slow
Do you have a driver's license?
Yeah, I think so...
Well well
Jon? Jon from Arnarfjord?
Hah
Jon from Arnarfjord, don't you remember me?
Sven
Sven from Sugandafjord like I was
sometimes called?
We sometimes met up between fishing
tours back in the day
I'm sure it's been thirty or forty years
See, you were dating a...
Girl from Patreksfjord
What was her name again?
Berg-something. Bergthora or Bergrun.
Hah, Jon from Arnarfjord
That's your mother, right?
Yep
Hello there, ma'am
You remember
me...?
And, where are you headed?
South
To Reykjavik?
Eyrarbakki
Eyrarbakki? Got relatives there?
My mom
Your mom has relatives there?
Yes
Hmm...
Plan on staying long?
Mom is going to rest there
Do they have a sanatorium there?
She doesn't need a rest, she's
dead
No, of course not
Uh.. Jon
Your driver's license is
getting a little worn
And I have to encourage you to have the car
inspected at your earliest convenience
Or just the next car repair shop
I really should...
Ground your car right
here and now, but...
You know, for
old times sake
And not to mention your mother
I'm going to give you
an opportunity to rectify this, alright
Okay
I don't say this very often, but in
Gods name, drive a little faster
Or take the local gravel roads
Wouldn't that work better for you?
Oh, are you...
Are you going to
watch the comet tonight?
It's going to be spectacular
Safe travels Jon
Maniac!