Hey.
Come.
Fucking hell, man.
Where did you learn to drive, huh?!
Hey man...
What's wrong with you, huh?!
No need to get violent.
Violent?!
How is one supposed to react to...
Attempted murder, huh?
Attempted murder?!
Yeah.
Fucking hell, man.
What are you thinking, man?!
You're endagering everyone here!
This is completely ridiculous, man!
What's wrong with you?!
Ugh!
New Caption
Good morning.
What's going on?
Ask this maniac!
He's endagering everyone here!
Drives around at 30km an hour...
(stuttering) on... on... on...
Hold your horses,
and come with me over here for a second.
New Caption
Am I being arrested for trying to...
promote some minimal traffic conduct?
Take it easy.
Because of this idiot?
This maniac?
Take it easy.
No one is being arrested.
Just come over and talk to me.
Well now, how are you doing?
I'm doing fine.
That's quite the row of cars behind you.
Yep.
What are we talking about here?
The row of cars behind me...
At what speed were you driving?
The speedometer showed forty two.
That wouldn't excactly be called speeding, would it?
Nope.
No...
This won't work.
You can't drive so slow.
You are causing a lot of danger in traffic.
It's really dangerous.
Do you have a driver's license?
Yeah, I...
think so...
Well well,
if it isn't Jon from Arnarfjord.
Isn't it Jon from Arn...
Don't you remember me?
Sven?
Sven from Sugandafjord.
We sometimes met up between finshing tours back in the day.
I'm sure it's been thirty or forty years.
You were dating a girl from Patro.
Berg-something was her name.
Berg... Berg... Bergljot... Bergrun.
Heh, Jon from Arnarfjord.
Is that your mother?
Yep.
Hello ther, ma'am.
You remember me...?
Where are you headed?
South.
Into town?
Eyrarbakki.
Eyrarbakki?
Yeah.
Got relatives there?
My mom.
Your mom has relatives there?
Yes.
Okay... Plan on staying long?
Well...
She is going to...
rest there.
Mmm...
Do they have a sanatorium there?
Huh?
Yes, like a temporary rest-stay place.
She doesn't need to rest.
She's dead.
Hey Jon...
Your driver's license is getting a little worn.
And I have to encourage you to have the car inspected at your earliest convenience.
Preferably at a repair shop.
You see...
I really should ground your car right here and now...
but... you know, for old times sake,
and especially because of your mother...
I'm going to give you a chance to rectify this.
Okay?
Mhmm.
Well...
I think it would be best for you to...
take less frequently used roads.
And... I haven't said this before,
but for the love of god, drive a little faster.
Oh, are you going to watch the...
comet tonight?
It's going to be spectacular...
Okay then... Safe travels...
Maniac.