Tschuldigung!
Hallo!
Entschuldinggen Sie, wir können leider nicht an Inhen vorbei
Erm
Sorry
We cannot meet
No go back
Uh
No place to meet
Or make a u-turn
Make a u-turn
Very difficult to drive big car back
*Inaudible*
New Caption
Die Karte, bring mal die Karte!
Ugh, manege
Sag mal, was sind das für
Landeier doch
Schanzy
Look, look
Much shorter for you to drive back
Erm
We can't
Impossible
We foreigners are not used
Not used to drive roads like this
Can you back?
I think he wants us to back up
Can we?
No
Scheiße, verdammt nochmal!
Ey, was willst du dann?
Crazy people!
Nein, komm nicht her, bleib da
Ich bin ja doch!
Verdammte Scheiße dort!