Tschuldigung!
Entschuldigen sie?
Hallo!
Entschuldinggen Sie, wir können leider nicht an Inhen vorbei
Sorry
We cannot meet
No go back
Erm
Uh
No place to make u-turn
Very difficult to drive big car back
*Inaudible*
Erm
Die Karte, bring mal die Karte!
Ugh, manege
Sag mal, was sind das für landeier doch
Scheiße
Schanzy
Look, look
Much shorter for you to drive back
Erm
We can't
Impossible
We foreigners are not used to
Drive roads like this
Ja?
I think he wants us to back up
Can we?
No
Can you back?
Can we back up?
No
Are you going to give in to a Nazi?
Nazi?
Scheiße, verdammt nochmal!
Ey, was willst du dann?
You!
Crazy people!
Nein, komm nicht her, bleib da!
Ich bin ja doch!
Verdammte Scheiße, Mann