Tschuldigung!
Hallo!
Entschuldinggen Sie, wir können leider nicht an Inhen vorbei
Erm
Sorry
We cannot meet
No go back
No place to make u-turn
Or..
Very difficult to drive big car back
*Inaudible*
Ja
Die Karte, bring mal die Karte!
Ugh, Scheiße manege
Sag mal, was sind das für landeier doch
Schanzy
Look, look
Much shorter for you to drive back
Erm
We can't
Impossible
We foreigners are not used to
Drive roads like this
Ja?
Can you back?
Bite?
I think he wants us to back up
Can we?
No
Are you going to give in to a Nazi?
Nazi?
Scheiße, verdammt nochmal!
Ey, was willst du ey?
You!
Crazy people!
Nein, komm nicht her, bleib da!
Ich bin ja doch!
Verdammte Scheiße, ey
*Inaudible*